<?xml version="1.0" ?> 
<sms_api>
<sms><uniqueid>151</uniqueid><msisdn>27834132002</msisdn><message>Q3. Most of time i like to spend time with my friends, talking about life and what kind of life we are living</message><country>South Africa</country><timereceived>0000000 </timereceived></sms><sms><uniqueid>150</uniqueid><msisdn>27834132002</msisdn><message>Q4. I think the fish oil. When me and my brother go to the shop, we see that the 5 litre one will cost about R40 bucks.</message><country>South Africa</country><timereceived>0000000 </timereceived></sms><sms><uniqueid>149</uniqueid><msisdn>27834132002</msisdn><message>Q2. People would get a job, and also the goverment assist them to find a job. </message><country>South Africa</country><timereceived>0000000 </timereceived></sms><sms><uniqueid>148</uniqueid><msisdn>27834132002</msisdn><message>Q3. Most of my time i like to go with my friend to menlyn and talking about life. I like to look at the beautiful clothes that look nice and suit me. </message><country>South Africa</country><timereceived>0000000 </timereceived></sms><sms><uniqueid>147</uniqueid><msisdn>27834132002</msisdn><message>Q11. Why they are so good at soccer and why they are so talented? </message><country>South Africa</country><timereceived>0000000 </timereceived></sms><sms><uniqueid>146</uniqueid><msisdn>27834132002</msisdn><message>Q7. When living in the city, we eat junk food, and people who live in the village eat healthy food every day. City food is more expensive </message><country>South Africa</country><timereceived>0000000 </timereceived></sms><sms><uniqueid>145</uniqueid><msisdn>27834132002</msisdn><message>Q1. We have beautiful attractions link union buildings, Robben island and those places make south africa a great country </message><country>South Africa</country><timereceived>0000000 </timereceived></sms><sms><uniqueid>144</uniqueid><msisdn>27834132002</msisdn><message>Q8. I would like to know what are the effects of climate change in Canada and how have they used that to their advantage </message><country>South Africa</country><timereceived>0000000 </timereceived></sms><sms><uniqueid>143</uniqueid><msisdn>27834132002</msisdn><message>Q11 i would like 2 know if those children are having the same challenges like smoking drugs and drinking alcohol. And how do they cope with that. </message><country>South Africa</country><timereceived>0000000 </timereceived></sms><sms><uniqueid>142</uniqueid><msisdn>27834132002</msisdn><message>Q10. I think people will not have a better life without having water and food. They will not survive without. That  means water and food are survival means </message><country>South Africa</country><timereceived>0000000 </timereceived></sms><sms><uniqueid>141</uniqueid><msisdn>27834132002</msisdn><message>Q2. If they can stop crime in our towns and rural areas. If they can provide good education and teach us maths and science. And also we must help the poor </message><country>South Africa</country><timereceived>0000000 </timereceived></sms><sms><uniqueid>140</uniqueid><msisdn>27834132002</msisdn><message>Q3. I will like to spend my quality time in a library, because i like to read </message><country>South Africa</country><timereceived>0000000 </timereceived></sms><sms><uniqueid>139</uniqueid><msisdn>27834132002</msisdn><message>Q5, yes. Because i am living with my granmy and she is the only one to afford food. Sometimes when she have money, we buy that food </message><country>South Africa</country><timereceived>0000000 </timereceived></sms><sms><uniqueid>138</uniqueid><msisdn>27834132002</msisdn><message>Q6. No, i havent bought imported food because that idea never came to mind. I always support local products and that` s it </message><country>South Africa</country><timereceived>0000000 </timereceived></sms><sms><uniqueid>137</uniqueid><msisdn>27834132002</msisdn><message>Q10. When you want toget more health and more energy and be strong</message><country>South Africa</country><timereceived>0000000</timereceived></sms><sms><uniqueid>136</uniqueid><msisdn>27834132002</msisdn><message>Q7. Living in the city is better than living in the village because cities are more advanced. Villages are running short of water and electricity</message><country>South Africa</country><timereceived>0000000</timereceived></sms>
</sms_api>